This XML defines a mission set for a game scenario involving a Clam Ltd. oil rig and tanker. Here’s a compact breakdown of each mission block and what its attributes mean:

Top-level metadata:
- `meta`:
  - `type="2"`: Likely a mission pack/group type.
  - `max_spawned="1"`: Only one mission of this type can be active at a time.
  - `is_repeatable="true"`: Missions can be replayed.
- `definition_data`:
  - `vehicle_filename="oil_tanker.xml"`: Base ship/vehicle definition.
  - `vehicle_delivery_filename="rig_instrument.xml"`: Item/vehicle used for delivery missions.
  - `rig_team_size="7"`: Max rig crew.
  - `tanker_team_size="4"`: Max tanker crew.

Individual missions:

1. `<rig_evacuation>`
   - Title: “Clam Ltd. Evacuation”
   - Long: Fire on the rig; full evacuation to nearby hospital.
   - Objectives:
     - Obj 1: “Evacuate 4 workers” within 20 mins (difficulty 5).
     - Obj 2: “Evacuate all 7 workers” within 15 mins.
     - Obj 3: “Evacuate all workers efficiently” within 10 mins.
   - Uses `obj_1_count="4"`, implies full crew = 7 (from `rig_team_size`).

2. `<rig_inspection>`
   - Title: “Clam Ltd. Rig Inspection”
   - Long: Pick up safety inspectors from the airport and take them to the rig.
   - All three objective texts are identical: just transporting inspectors (likely single-step mission with no time/ count constraints specified here).

3. `<rig_inspection_alt>`
   - Title: “Clam Ltd. Inspection Phase 2”
   - Long: Inspectors are currently on the tanker; transport them to the rig for phase 2.
   - Same objective texts as `rig_inspection`; different starting location narrative.

4. `<rig_med_evac>`
   - Title: “Rig Worker Medevac”
   - Long: Evacuate an injured rig worker to the nearest hospital.
   - Objectives:
     - All three: “Evacuate casualty”, with increasing time pressure:
       - Obj 1: 20 mins
       - Obj 2: 15 mins
       - Obj 3: 10 mins

5. `<rig_deliver_parts>`
   - Title: “Clam Ltd. Equipment Delivery”
   - Long: Collect rig instruments from a research base and deliver to the rig.
   - Objectives:
     - Obj 1: “Deliver 1 rig instrument” within 120 mins.
     - Obj 2: “Deliver 2 rig instruments” within 120 mins.
     - Obj 3: “Deliver both rig instruments efficiently” (2 instruments) within 60 mins.
   - `difficulty="3"`.

6. `<tanker_inspection>`
   - Title: “Clam Ltd. Safety Inspection”
   - Long: Collect safety inspectors from the airport and transport them to the tanker.
   - Objectives: all just “Transport safety inspectors” (likely similar to `rig_inspection` but target is tanker).

7. `<tanker_inspection_alt>`
   - Title: “Clam Ltd. Inspection Phase 2”
   - Long: Inspectors are on the rig; transport them to the tanker for phase 2.
   - Same objective texts as the other inspection missions.

8. `<tanker_evacuation>`
   - Title: “Clam Ltd. Tanker Evacuation”
   - Long: Evacuate tanker crew to the nearby hospital.
   - Objectives:
     - Obj 1: “Evacuate 2 workers” (with `obj_1_count="2"`).
     - Obj 2: “Evacuate all 4 workers”.
     - Obj 3: “Evacuate all workers efficiently”.
   - `difficulty="3"`. No explicit time limits defined here.

9. `<tanker_tow>`
   - Title: “Tanker Tow”
   - Long: Broken-down tanker must be towed back to the rig.
   - Objectives: all “Tow tanker to rig”.
   - Time: 150 mins for obj 1/2/3 (no escalating time pressure).
   - `difficulty="3"`.

If you tell me what you want to change (e.g., difficulty, times, counts, descriptions, or add/remove missions), I can rewrite this XML accordingly.